const questionsLimit=10;

const quiz = [
    {
        question: "I ____ my homework.",
        answer: "have done",
        choices: ["do", "have done", "doing", "have doing"]
    },

    {
        question: "She ____ her breakfast.",
        answer: "has done",
        choices: ["does", "doing", "has done", "has doing"]
    },

    {
        question: "He ____ his lunch.",
        answer: "has eaten",
        choices: ["have done", "has eaten", "eating", "does"]
    },

    {
        question: "She ____ her room." ,
        answer: "has cleaned",
        choices: ["does", "doing", "has cleaned", "cleans"]
    },

    {
        question: "We ____ our trip.",
        answer: "have planned",
        choices: ["does", "have planned", "doing", "plan"]
    },

    {
        question: "He ____ his car.",
        answer: "has washed",
        choices: ["do", "does", "doing", "has washed"]
    },

    {
        question: "They ____ their exams.",
        answer: "have finished",
        choices: ["have finished", "do", "finished", "does"]
    },

    {
        question: "She ____ to the new song.",
        answer: "has listened",
        choices: ["does", "has listened", "doing", "listening"]
    },

    {
        question: "We ____ our friends.",
        answer: "have been meeting",
        choices: ["have met", "met", "have been meeting", "meeting"]
    },

    {
        question: "I ____ my coffee.",
        answer: "have finished",
        choices: ["have finished", "do", "does", "finished"]
    },

    {
        question: "He ____ to the doctor.",
        answer: "has gone",
        choices: ["do", "does", "doing", "has gone"]
    },

    {
        question: "They ____ their lunch.",
        answer: "have eaten",
        choices: ["does", "have eaten", "doing", "eat"]
    },

    {
        question: "She ____ her job.",
        answer: "left",
        choices: ["does", "doing", "has left", "left"]
    },

    {
        question: "We ____ the movie.",
        answer: "have seen",
        choices: ["have seen", "see", "does", "seen"]
    },

    {
        question: "He ____ his breakfast.",
        answer: "has eaten",
        choices: ["doing", "does", "has eaten", "eats"]
    },


    {
        question: "We ____ the movie.",
        answer: "have watched",
        choices: ["have watched", "watch", "has watched", "watching"]
    },


    {
        question: "They ____ the book.",
        answer: "have read",
        choices: ["do", "does", "doing", "have read"]
    },

    {
        question: "My parents ____ to Paris.",
        answer: "have been",
        choices: ["have been", "are", "has been", "is"]
    },

    {
        question: "She ____ her room.",
        answer: "has cleaned",
        choices: ["does", "doing", "has cleaned", "cleans"]
    },

    {
        question: "We ____ our trip.",
        answer: "have planned",
        choices: ["does", "have planned", "doing", "plan"]
    },

    {
        question: "He ____ his car.",
        answer: "has washed",
        choices: ["do", "does", "doing", "has washed"]
    },

    {
        question: "They ____ their exams.",
        answer: "have finished",
        choices: ["have finished", "do", "finished", "does"]
    },

    {
        question: "She ____ to the new song.",
        answer: "has listened",
        choices: ["does", "has listened", "doing", "listening"]
    },

    {
        question: "We ____ our friends.",
        answer: "have been meeting",
        choices: ["have met", "met", "have been meeting", "meeting"]
    },

    {
        question: "I ____ my coffee.",
        answer: "have finished",
        choices: ["have finished", "do", "does", "finished"]
    },



]